<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card - Taiwan Foreign Talent Community</title>
    <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card - Taiwan Foreign Talent Community</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Taiwan Employment Gold Card?</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/what-is-taiwan-gold-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/what-is-taiwan-gold-card/</guid>
      <description>Taiwan Employment Gold Card is a special visa launched in 2018 to attract &amp;ldquo;special&amp;rdquo; talents in Taiwan. It gives you the right to stay and work in Taiwan from 1 year up to 3 years (renewable). You&amp;rsquo;ll be able to work for any company, start a new business, have great tax incentives, benefit Taiwan healtchare system, and bring your family with you.
The application is online, and straigh forward. Approbation is based on your existing skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualifications</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</guid>
      <description>Do I qualify? In order to qualify for an Employment Gold Card your skills must be related to one of eight areas: Science and Technology, Economics, Education, Culture and Art, Sport, Finance, Law and Architecture. You must select which single ministry is most relevant, and in most cases also select a specific entry in the list of that qualifications in that particular area for your application. Use the Gold Card Qualification Wizard to find the relevant choices for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gold Card Application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</guid>
      <description>How to apply? Application is done online. Once you have determined how you are qualified, gather the required documents:
 digital copy of your passport digital copy of your passport photo locate your previous Taiwanese visa and residence permit (if any) dates of any times you worked in Taiwan digital copies of all documents needed to support your application  Note: all digital copies need to be &amp;lt;1MB in size in image or PDF format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After submitting your application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</guid>
      <description>What happens after you submit your application?  Your qualifications will be assessed.  First, the Ministry of Labor will attempt to sign off on the work permit. If it can do this itself (eg you apply based on the salary criteria and provide the right documents), your application will be swift (one case took just two days). If the Ministry of Labor can&amp;rsquo;t vet your skills, it will call in the appropriate Ministry (eg &amp;ldquo;Science and Technology) to assist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>