<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card</title>
    <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualifications</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</guid>
      <description>Do I qualify? In order to qualify for an Employment Gold Card your skills must be related to one of eight areas: Science and Technology, Economics, Education, Culture and Art, Sport, Finance, Law and Architecture. You must select which of these is most relevant, and in most cases also select a specific entry in the list of that qualifications in that particular area for your application. See How to apply for Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Employment Gold Card</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gold Card Application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</guid>
      <description>Who can I talk to about this? You&amp;rsquo;re in for some serious luck here! The Gold Card comes with some direct contacts who are high level and exceptionally helpful. However, first it is critical to understand that this program is a collaboration of disparate Government departments who aren&amp;rsquo;t necessarily in constant communication with each other. You will need to choose a department to contact depending on the stage of your application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After submitting your application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</guid>
      <description>What happens after you submit your application?  Your qualifications will be assessed.  First, the Ministry of Labor will attempt to sign off on the work permit. If it can do this itself (eg you apply based on the salary criteria and provide the right documents), your application will be swift (one case took just two days). If the Ministry of Labor can&amp;rsquo;t vet your skills, it will call in the appropriate Ministry (eg &amp;ldquo;Science and Technology) to assist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>