<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card</title>
    <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualifications</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</guid>
      <description>Do I qualify? See How to apply for Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Employment Gold Card
Is there an age restriction? Not really. However it is expected that gold card holders will have at least five years of work experience.
Do I need to have a high salary to apply for a Gold Card? No. Most industries have a category where applicants with a salary greater than NT$160,000 qualify. However, this is only one category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gold Card Application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</guid>
      <description>Who can I talk to about this? See How to apply for Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Employment Gold Card
How to apply? See How to apply for Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Employment Gold Card
Is there a &amp;ldquo;general&amp;rdquo; application category or must I select a specific industry? There is no &amp;ldquo;general&amp;rdquo; application category. You must select a ministry to assess your skills. See How to apply for Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Employment Gold Card
How long does the application take?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After submitting your application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</guid>
      <description>How do you get your physical card? Either at the National Immigration Agency service centres (in Taiwan) or at your local Taiwanese diplomatic post overseas. You selected where during your application.
How long does the application take? A perfect application takes 30 days, if your supporting documents are accepted the first time around. If you are asked for tweaks to your supporting documents, expect 50-60 days.
What is a &amp;ldquo;Resident Authorization Letter&amp;rdquo;?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>