<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card - Taiwan Foreign Talent Community</title>
    <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gold Card Application FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card - Taiwan Foreign Talent Community</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is the Gold Card?</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/what-is-taiwan-gold-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/what-is-taiwan-gold-card/</guid>
      <description>The Taiwan Employment Gold Card is a combined visa, work permit and residence permit launched in 2018 to attract professional talent in Taiwan. The card gives you the right to stay and work in Taiwan for 1 year to 3 years, and you can apply online without sponsorship. The card comes with open work rights, so you may work for any (or multiple) company in Taiwan or start your own business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I qualify?</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/qualifications/</guid>
      <description>In order to qualify for an Employment Gold Card your skills must be related to one of eight areas: Science and Technology, Economics, Education, Culture and Art, Sport, Finance, Law and Architecture. You must select which single ministry is most relevant, and in most cases also select a specific entry in the list of that qualifications in that particular area for your application. Use the Gold Card Qualification Check to find the relevant choices for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gold Card Application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/application/</guid>
      <description>Application is done online. Once you have determined how you are qualified, gather the required documents:
 Digital copy of your passport Digital copy of your passport photo Your previous Taiwanese visa and residence permit (if any) Dates of any times you worked in Taiwan Digital copies of all documents needed to support your application   ⓘ All digital copies need to be &amp;lt;1MB in size in image or PDF format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After submitting your application</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-submitting-application/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations on getting the application in.
At this point you will receive an email telling you to pay. If you didn&amp;rsquo;t get it, check your email address was correct.
You must now go through the payment steps in order for your application to be considered.
Log in to the portal at: https://coa.immigration.gov.tw/coa-frontend/four-in-one/entry/golden-card
click &amp;ldquo;Online Payment&amp;rdquo; and select &amp;ldquo;Permit Payment&amp;rdquo;, then follow the steps. Fees are non-refundable, even if your application is unsuccessful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After passing skill assessment</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-passing-skill-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/application-faq/after-passing-skill-assessment/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations! The long and hard part is now over: you&amp;rsquo;ve been deemed sufficiently skilled to hold a Gold Card.
All that&amp;rsquo;s left is Identity Verification and you can collect your card!
Identity Verification 🕑 1-2 weeks
Congratulations on passing the skill assessment. It&amp;rsquo;s now time to deliver your passport for identity verification.
 If you are overseas, you should visit the nearest Taiwanese diplomatic post If you are in Taiwan, you must visit the Bureau of Consular Affairs  You will also need to take a copy of the &amp;ldquo;Passport Submission Notice&amp;rdquo;, which is found in the &amp;ldquo;Download&amp;rdquo; menu after logging in to the portal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
