<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gold Card Holders FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card - Taiwan Foreign Talent Community</title>
    <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gold Card Holders FAQ on Taiwan Gold Card - Taiwan Foreign Talent Community</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>At Work</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/at-work/</guid>
      <description>What do I need to tell my employer about the Gold Card? Your Gold Card is a four-in-one document that contains your work permit, residence visa, reentry permit and Alien Residence Certificate. You have open work rights and they do not need to apply for a work permit or visa for you.
What happens if I lose my job? You may simply find a new job. Your Gold Card is not sponsored by your employer and will not be affected by a change of job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Insurance</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/health-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/health-insurance/</guid>
      <description>What health insurance is available in Taiwan? All who are eligible for National Health Insurance (NHI) must enrol into the program, which provides comprehensive and inexpensive coverage. Eligibility varies slightly depending on your employment status. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t eligible for NHI then there are also a range of local and international private health insurance options available.
You can check the NHI website for more details.
How do I enrol into the program If you have an employer in Taiwan then they will enrol you into the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/life-in-taiwan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/life-in-taiwan/</guid>
      <description>How do I find a place to rent? Renting is common in Taiwan, and there are a large range of types of dwellings available at diffrerent price points. The most popular property search website is 591. Unlike in some other countries, real estate agents offering rental properties in Taiwan are typically only brokers who present prospective tenants to landlords for a fee and you will normally deal directly with a landlord from lease signing onward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration Pathways</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/migration-pathways/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/migration-pathways/</guid>
      <description>Should I switch from an APRC to a Gold Card? According to NIA officials, no. They stress that this card is nonrenewable and you must go through the application process again toward the end of the gold card. One way of looking at that is that the Foreign Special Professional program could change to the point where one no longer qualifies. APRC is therefore “safer” in the long term.
Consider also if the program doesn’t change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/tax/</guid>
      <description>Note: Everyone has a different situation. Please consult an accountant before relying on content from this section. Terms.
 How do I apply for the tax relief for Foreign Special Professionals? As a Gold Card holder working in Taiwan for the first time, for the portion of your salary over NT $3 million, half of it can be excluded from your effective income for your first three years of residence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/family/</guid>
      <description>Can my spouse and children come with me if I get a Gold Card? Yes, for children under 20 years old and married spouses this is no problem.
Can my spouse work, if they join me in Taiwan as a dependant? The Gold Card does not provide for a work permit for dependants of the card holder. Your spouse should get their own work permit.
What happens if I get married to a Taiwanese citizen while on a Gold Card?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renewal &amp; Validity</title>
      <link>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/validity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taiwangoldcard.com/goldcard-holders-faq/validity/</guid>
      <description>How long is a gold card valid? By default, between one and three years. If you are concerned your card (or underlying visa/work permit) may have become invalid or expired, you can check with the National Immigration Agency.
Can I renew my gold card? No. There is no renewal capability for a Gold Card. You must complete the same application process you went through for your first card for all subsequent cards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
